Guide to the Stanford University Faculty Publications
Stanford University. Libraries.
- Books, Series 1
  - Kelley, Truman Lee, The Influence of Nurture Upon Native Differences, 1926 (Box 32)
  - Kelley, Truman Lee, Educational Guidance: An Experimental Study in the Analysis and Prediction of Ability of High School Pupils, 1914 (Box 32)
  - Kelley, Truman Lee, Interpretation of Educational Measurements, 1927 (Box 32)
  - Kelley, Truman Lee, Scientfic Method: Its Function in Research and in Education, 1929 (Box 32)
  - Kellogg, Charlotte, Women of Belgium: Turning Tragety to Triumph, 1917 (Box 32)
  - Kellogg, Vernon L., Insect Stories, 1908 (Box 32)
  - Kellogg, Vernon L., Darwinism Today, 1907 (Box 33)
  - Kellogg, Vernon L., Elementary Zoology, 1901 (Box 33)
  - Kellogg, Vernon L., Beyond War: A Chapter in the Natural History of Man, 1912 (Box 33)
  - Kellogg, Vernon L., First Lessons in Zoology, 1903 (Box 33)
  - Kellogg, Vernon L., Headquarters Nights, 1917 (Box 33)
  - Kellogg, Vernon L., Pamphlets: 1892-1899 (Box 34)
  - Kellogg, Vernon L., Papers: 1904-1920 (Box 34)
  - Kellogg, Vernon L., Mes Soirees Au Grand Quartier, 1919 (Box 34)
  - Kellogg, Vernon L., Herbert Hoover: The Man and His Work, 1920 (Box 34)
  - Kellogg, Vernon L., Evolution: The Way of Man, 1924 (Box 34)
  - Kellogg, Vernon L., In and Out of Florence, 1910 (Box 34)
  - Kellogg, Vernon L., Human Life as the Biologist Sees It, 1922 (Box 34)
  - Kellogg, Vernon L., Vernon Kellogg 1867-1937, 1939 (Box 35)
  - Kellogg, Vernon L. and David S. Jordan, Animal Life: A First Book of Zoology, 1900 (Box 32)
  - Kellogg, Vernon L. and David S. Jordan, Evolution and Animal Life, 1907 (Box 33)
  - Kellogg, Vernon L. and David S. Jordan, The Food Problem, 1917 (Box 33)
  - Kellogg, Vernon L. and David S. Jordan, Germany in the War and After, 1919 (Box 33)
  - Kellogg, Vernon L. and Gaston Bodart, Losses of Lofe in Modern Wars; Military Selection and Race Deterioration, 1916 (Box 35)
  - Kellogg, Vernon L. and John H. Comstock, Elements of Insect Anatomy, 1899 (Box 33)
  - Kellogg, Vernon L. and John H. Comstock, The Elements of Insect Anatomy; third edition, 1901 (Box 34)
  - Kellogg, Vernon L. and John H. Comstock, The Elements of Insect Anatomy, 1895 (Box 34)
  - Kellogg, Vernon L. and Oliver P. Jenkins, Lessons in Nature Study, 1900 (Box 35)
  - Kimball, Dexter S., I Remember, 1953 (Box 35)
  - Krehbiel, Edward B., Nationalism, War and Society, 1916 (Box 35)
  - Krehbiel, Edward B., The Interdict: Its History and its Operation, 1909 (Box 35)
  - Krehbiel, Edward B., Social France at the Time of Philip Augustus, 1912 (Box 35)
  - Krupp, Marcus A., Physician's Handbook, Seventh Edition, 1941 (Box 4)
  - Lanz, Henry, Collected Papers in Russian (Box 35)
  - Lanz, Henry, Den Etiska Objektiviteten, 1937 (Box 35)
  - LaPiere, Richard T., Social Change, 1965 (Box 36)
  - LaPiere, Richard T., A Theory in Social Control, 1954 (Box 36)
  - LaPiere, Richard T., Zoon Van Han, 1937 (Box 36)
  - LaPiere, Richard T., Son of Han, 1937 (Box 36)
  - LaPiere, Richard T., When the Living Strive, 1941 (Box 37)
  - LaPiere, Richard T., The Freudian Ethic: An Analysis of the Subversion of American Character, 1959 (Box 37)
  - LaPiere, Richard T., Sociology, 1946 (Box 37)
  - LaPiere, Richard T., Collective Behavior, 1938 (Box 37)
  - LaPiere, Richard T. and Paul R. Farnsworth, Social Psychology; second edition, 1942 (Box 36)
  - LaPiere, Richard T. and Paul R. Farnsworth, Social Psychology; first edition, 1936 (Box 36)
  - LaPiere, Richard T. and Paul R. Farnsworth, Social Psychology; third edition, 1949 (Box 37)
  - Lawson, Anstruther A., Papers: 1898 - 1903 (Box 37)
  - Lemos, Pedro J., The Art Teacher: A Book for Children and Teachers, 1935 (Box 38)
  - Lewis, Janet, The Wife of Martin Guerre, 1941 (Box 37)
  - Luther, Martin, Schriften; edited by William Carruth, 1899 (Box 10)
  - Lutz, Harley Leist, Public Finance, 1924 (Box 38)
  - Lutz, Ralph, Die Beziehungen zwischen Deutschland und den Vereinigten Staaten wahrend des Sezessionskrieges, 1911 (Box 38)
  - MacFarland, Frank Mace, Memoirs of the California Academy of Sciences, Vol. 6: Studies of Opisthobranchiate Mollusks of the Pacific Coast of North America, 1966 (Box 38)
  - Malik, Charles et. al., The Conservative Papers, 1964 (Box 23)
  - Marshall, Hubert and Robert J. Young, Public Administration of Florida's Natural Resources, 1953 (Box 38)
  - Marshall, Hubert R., Science and State Government in California (Box 60)
  - Marshall, Thomas Maitland, University of California Publications in History, Vol.2: A History of the Western Boundary of the Louisiana Purchase, 1819-1841, 1914 (Box 38)
  - Martin, Ernest Whitney, The Birds of the Latin Poets, 1914 (Box 38)
  - Martin, Lillien J., Ein experimenteller Beitrag zur Erforschung des Unterbewussten, 1915 (Box 39)
  - Martin, Lillien J., American Journal of Psychology, Vol. 17, January 1913: The Electical Supply, and Certain New Additions to the Laboratory Equipment, in the Stanford University Psychological Laboratory (Box 39)
  - Martin, Lillien J., American Journal of Psychology, Vol. 17, April 1906: The Electrical Supply in the New Psychology Laboratory at the Leland Stanford, Jr., University (Box 39)
  - Martin, Lillien J., The Psychology Review, Vol. 13, No. 3: An Experimental Study of Fechner's Principles of Aesthetics, 1906 (Box 39)
  - Martin, Lillien J., American Journal of Psychology, Vol. 16, No. 1: Experimental Prospecticting in the Field of the Comic (Box 39)
  - Martin, Lillien J., Monatsschrift fur Psychiatrie und Neurologie, Vol. 31, No. 4: Uber die Lokalisation der visuellen Bilder bei normalen und anormalen Personen, 1912 (Box 39)
  - Martin, Lillien J., Zeitschrift fur Psychologie und Physiologie der Sinnesorgane: Zeitschrift fur Psychologie, 1912 (Box 39)
  - Martin, Lillien J., American Journal of Psychology, Vol. 26, April 1915: Ghosts and the Projection of Visual Images (Box 39)
  - Martin, Lillien J., The Psychological Review, Vol. 22, No. 4, July 1915: An Experimental COntribution to the Investigation of the Subconscious (Box 39)
  - Martin, Lillien J., Zur begrundung und anwendung der suggestionsmethode in der normal psychologie, 1907 (Box 39)
  - Martin, Lillien J., Uber Asthetische Synasthesie, 1909 (Box 39)
  - Martin, Lillien J., Zur Lehre von den Bewegungsvorstellungen, 1899 (Box 39)
  - Martin, Lillien J., Die Projektionsmethode und die Lokalisation visueller und anderer Vorstellungsbilder, 1912 (Box 39)
  - Martin, Lillien J. and Clare deGruchy, The Home in a Democracy, 1938 (Box 39)
  - Martin, Lillien J. and Clare deGruchy, Salvaging Old Age, 1930 (Box 39)
  - Martin, Lillien J. and G. E. Muller, Zur Analyse der Unterschiedsempfindlichkeit, 1899 (Box 39)
  - Marx, Guido H. and Albert W. Smith, Machine Design, 1915 (Box 39)
  - Matzke, John E., Cinna, ou La Clemence d'Auguste; written by Pierre Corneille, 1903 (Box 39)
  - Matzke, John E., Horace; written by Pierre Corneille, 1904 (Box 39)
  - Matzke, John E., Hernani; written by Victor Hugo, 1904 (Box 40)
  - Matzke, John E., First Spanish Readings, 1897 (Box 40)
  - Mears, Eliot Grinnell, Modern Turkey: A Politico-Economic Interperetation, 1908-1923 Inclusive, With Selected Chapters by Representative Authorities, 1924 (Box 40)
  - Mears, Eliot Grinnell, Vol. 1: Articles in U.S. Commerce Reports, 1919 (Box 40)
  - Mears, Eliot Grinnell, Vol. 2: Articles in U.S. Commerce Reports, 1920 (Box 40)
  - Mears, Eliot Grinnell, Vol. 3: Publications, 1925 (Box 40)
  - Mears, Eliot Grinnell, Pacific Ocean Handbook, 1944 (Box 42)
  - Mears, Eliot Grinnell and Mathew O. Tobriner, Principles and Practices of Cooperative Marketing, 1926 (Box 40)
  - Merrill, Catherine, The Man Shakespeare and Other Essays, analysis by Anderson, Melville B., 1902 (Box 4)
  - Meyer, Arthur William, Human Generation: Conclusions of Burdach, Dollinger and von Baer, 1956 (Box 41)
  - Meyer, Arthur William and Franklin P. Mall, Contributions to Embryology, Vol. 12, No. 56: Studies on Abortuses: A Survey of Pathologic Ova in the Carnegie Embryological Collection, 1921 (Box 41)
  - Miller, G. A., Papers 1900-1905 (Box 41)
  - Miller, Walter, Papers 1893-1898 (Box 41)
  - Mirrielees, Edith R., Stanford Mosaic: Reminiscences of the First Seventy Years at Stanford University, 1962 (Box 41)
  - Mirrielees, Edith R., Significant Contemporary Stories, 1929 (Box 42)
  - Mirrielees, Edith R., Writing of the Short Story, 1929 (Box 42)
  - Mirrielees, Edith R., Short Stories of America,edited by, 1937 (Box 42)
  - Momaday, N. Scott, The Way to Rainy Mountain, 1967 (Box 42)
  - Morgan, Baynard Quincy, Carl Schurz, 1829-1906: A Great German-American (Box 42)
  - Morgan, Baynard Quincy, Das Gluck von Lautenthal; written by Paul Ernst (Box 42)
  - Mosher, Clelia Duel, Personal Hygiene for Women, 1927 (Box 42)
  - Mosher, Clelia Duel, The Mosher Survey: Sexual Attitudes of 45 Victorian Women, 1980 (Box 42)
  - Murray, Augustus Taber, Greek Composition for Colleges, 1902 (Box 42)
  - Nash, Herbert C., The Train Robber: A Farce in One Act, 1895 (Box 42)
  - Neidig, William J., The First Wardens and Other Poems, 1905 (Box 42)
  - Neilson, N. P. and Frederic W. Cozens, Achievement Scales in Physical Education Activities for Boys and Girls in Elementary and Junior High Schools, 1934 (Box 42)
  - Neilson, N. P. and Frederic W. Cozens and Martin H. Trieb, Physical Education Achievement Scales for Boys in Secondary Schools, 1936 (Box 42)
  - Newcomer, Alphonso G., American Literature, 1905 (Box 42)
  - Newcomer, Alphonso G., English Literature, 1905 (Box 43)
  - Newcomer, Alphonso G., Memorial Ode and Other Poems, 1913 (Box 43)
  - Newcomer, Alphonso G., A Practical Course in English Composition, 1893 (Box 43)
  - Newcomer, Alphonso G., Elements of Rhetoric, 1899 (Box 43)
  - Newcomer, Alphonso G. and Alice E. Andrews, Twelve Centuries of English Poetry and Prose, 1910 (Box 43)
  - Newcomer, Alphonso G. and Samuel S. Seward, Rhetoric in Practice, 1905 (Box 43)
  - Newcomer, Alphonso G. et. al., Three Centuries of American Poetry and Prose; revised edition, 1917 (Box 43)
  - Newsom, J. F., Papers 1897-1903 (Box 43)
  - Nielsen, Oswald, University Administration in Practice; translated into Japanese by Nobumoto Ohama, 1960 (Box 43)
  - Olsson-Seffer, P., Papers 1902-1909 (Box 44)
  - O'Malley, Charles Donald and John Saunders, Andreas Vesalius Bruxellensis: The Bloodletting Letter of 1539; An Annotated Translation and Study of the Evolution of Vesalius's Schientific Development, 1943 (Box 44)
  - Osorio, Luis Enrique, Vision de America, 1961 (Box 44)
  - Otis, Arthur S., Light Velocity and Relativity, 1963 (Box 44)
  - Packenham, Robert A. et. al., Revista de Direito Publico e Ciencia Politica, 1965 (Box 44)
  - Peirce, George James, A Text-Book of Plant Physiology, 1903 (Box 44)
  - Pellissier, Robert, Letters from a Chasseur a Pied, 1917 (Box 44)
  - Perrine, Frederic A. C., A Portrait of Frederic A. C. Perrine, A. M., D. Sc., 1908 (Box 44)
  - Raffel, Sidney, A Laboratory Manual of Immunology (Box 60)
  - Read, J. Marion, A History of the California Academy of Medicine, 1930 (Box 44)
  - Ready, W. B., The Great Disciple and Other Stories, 1951 (Box 44)
  - Reining, Charles, A Study of Verbs Compounded with Aus, Ein, etc.... (Box 60)
  - Richardson, George M., Papers: 1896-1901 (Box 44)
  - Richardson, George M., Laboratory Manual and Principles of Chemistry, 1894 (Box 44)
  - Richardson, George M., The Foundations of Stereo Chemistry: Memoirs by Pasteur, Van't Hoff, Lebel, and Wislicenus, 1901 (Box 44)
  - Robinson, Edgar Eugene, The Presidential Vote 1896-1932, 1934 (Box 45)
  - Robinson, Edgar Eugene, The Evolution of American Political Parties: A Sketch of Party Development, 1924 (Box 45)
  - Robinson, Edgar Eugene, The Presidential Vote 1936; supplement to The Presidential Vote 1896-1932, 1940 (Box 45)
  - Robinson, Edgar Eugene and Paul C. Edwards, The Memoirs of Ray Lyman Wilbur, 1960 (Box 45)
  - Robinson, Edgar Eugene and Victor J. West, The Foreign Policy of Woodrow Wilson 1913-1917 (Box 45)
  - Rogers, Austin Flint, Introduction to the Study of Minerals and Rocks: A Combined Text-Book and Pocket Manual, 1921 (Box 45)
  - Rogers, Austin Flint and Paul F. Kerr, Thin-Section Mineralogy, 1933 (Box 45)
  - Ruff, Wesley K., Gymnastics: Beginner to Competitor (Box 60)
  - Russell, Frances Theresa, Satire in the Victorian Novel, 1920 (Box 46)
  - Russell, Frances Theresa, Touring Utopia: The Realm of Constructive Humanism, 1932 (Box 46)
  - Sanford, Fernando, Elements of Physics, 1902 (Box 46)
  - Sanford, Fernando, The Electrical Charges of Atoms and Ions, 1919 (Box 46)
  - Sanford, Fernando, Studies in Electricity, No. 1: Some Observations Upon the Conductivity of a Copper Wire in Various Dielectrics, 1892 (Box 46)
  - Sanford, Fernando, Papers: 1892-1899 (Box 46)
  - Sangiorgi, Roberto Benaglia and Grace Knopp, La Ciudad de los Cesares; written by Manuel Rojas, 1951 (Box 46)
  - Say, Leon, Turgot, translated by Melville B. Anderson, 1888 (Box 4)
  - Schaffner, Bertram, Group Processes: Transactions of the Second Conference of October 9, 10, 11, and 12, 1955, 1956 (Box 6)
  - Schenck, Hubert G. and Philip W. Reinhart, Oligocene Arcid Pelecypods of the Genus Anadara, 1938 (Box 46)
  - Schiller, Friedrich, Die Braut von Meffina; edited by William Carruth, 1901 (Box 10)
  - Schiller, Friedrich, Wallenstein; edited by William Carruth, 1901 (Box 10)
  - Schiller, Friedrich, Wilhelm Tell; edited by William Carruth, 1898 (Box 10)
  - Schiller, Friedrich, Ekkehard; introduction by William Carruth, 1895 (Box 11)
  - Schilpp, Paul Arthur, Publications in Philosophy, Vol. III: Lectures Delivered Under the Auspices of the Pacific Philosophy Club in Anderson Hall During 1933-1934 (Box 9)
  - Schmidt, Otto E. L., Basic Dermatology (Box 61)
  - Schnittkind, Henry T., The Poets of the Future: A College Anthology for 1916-1917 (Box 46)
  - Schramm, Wilbur, The Process and Effects of Mass Communication; translated to Spanish, 1954 (Box 47)
  - Schultz, E. W., Laboratory Manual of Medical Bacteriology [1935, 1946, 1954] (Box 61)
  - Schwartz, William Leonard, The Imaginative Interpretation of the Far East in Modern French Literature, 1800-1925, 1927 (Box 47)
  - Schwartz, William Leonard, Revue de Litterature Comparee, Octobre-Decembre, 1926 (Box 47)
  - Schwartz, William Leonard, Le Monde ou L'On S'Ennuie; written by Edouard Pailleron, 1928 (Box 47)
  - Schwartz, William Leonard, French Romantic Poetry: An Anthology, 1932 (Box 47)
  - Searles, Colbert, Le Cid; written by Pierre Corneille, 1912 (Box 47)
  - Searles, Colbert, Francois le Champi; written by George Sand, 1914 (Box 47)
  - Searles, Colbert, Papers: 1911-1914 (Box 47)
  - Searles, Colbert, Andromaque; written by Jean Racine, 1914 (Box 47)
  - Shedd, Solon, Bibliography of the Geology and Mineral Resources of California for the Years 1931 to 1936, Inclusive, 1928 (Box 47)
  - Shedd, Solon, Bibliography of the Geology and Mineral Resources of California to December 31, 1930, 1933 (Box 47)
  - Shoup, Paul, Side Tracks from the Main Line, 1924 (Box 47)
  - Simon, Jules, Victor Cousin, translated by Melville B. Anderson, 1888 (Box 4)
  - Smith, Albert W., Poems in Varying Moods, 1934 (Box 48)
  - Smith, Albert W., Elementary Machine Design, 1895 (Box 48)
  - Smith, Albert W., Materials of Machines, 1902 (Box 48)
  - Smith, Albert W., The Giant and Other Nonsense Verse, 1910 (Box 48)
  - Smith, Albert W. and Guido H. Marx, Machine Design; first edition, 1905 (Box 48)
  - Smith, Albert W. and Guido H. Marx, Machine Design; fourth edition, 1915 (Box 48)
  - Smith, Gilbert M., Cryptogamic Botany, v.1: Algae and Fungi, 1938 (Box 49)
  - Smith, Gilbert M., Cryptogamic Botany, v.2: Bryophytes and Pteridophytes, 1938 (Box 49)
  - Smith, Gilbert M. et. al., A Textbook of General Botany; second edition, 1928 (Box 48)
  - Smith, Gilbert M. et. al., A Textbook of General Botany; third edition, 1935 (Box 48)
  - Smith, Gilbert M. et. al., A Textbook of General Botany; fourth edition, 1947 (Box 48)
  - Smith, James Perrin, Papers: 1894-1927 (Box 49)
  - Smith, James Perrin, Lower Triassic Ammonoids of North America, 1932 (Box 49)
  - Smith, Leland, Hankbook of Harmonic Analysis (Box 60)
  - Smith, Mary R., Appletons' Popular Science Monthly, v. 48, Nov. 1895: Recent Tendancies in the Education of Women (Box 49)
  - Smith, Ralph J., Engineering as a Career, 1962 (Box 51)
  - Snyder, John O., Faculty Publications (Box 50)
  - Snyder, John O. et. al., Journal of the College of Science, Imperial University of Tokyo: A Catalogue of the Fishes of Japan, 1913 (Box 49)
  - Sokol, Anthony Eugene and Helena Nye, Beruhmte Forscher Und Ihre Beitrage: Ein Wissenschaftliches Lesebuch, 1938 (Box 51)
  - Sophocles, The Antigone of Sophocles; translated by H. R. Fairclough and A. T. Murray, 1902 (Box 20)
  - Spiegelberg, Frederic, Sivananda in Stanford University: A Review of Sri Swami Sivananda's Works, 1958 (Box 51)
  - Spiegelberg, Frederic, In Sivananda Literature; written by Sri Swami Sivananda, 1960 (Box 51)
  - Spoehr, Herman Augustus, Essays on Science, 1956 (Box 51)
  - Stearns, Herman D., The Effect of Proximity to the Sea on Thunderstorm Periods, 1898 (Box 51)
  - Stebbins, Horatio Ward, An Outline of Elementary Thermodynamics, 1933 (Box 51)
  - Stephens, Mark, Three Mile Island, 1980 (Box 51)
  - Stillman, John Maxson, Paracelsus, 1920 (Box 51)
  - Stillman, John Maxson, The Story of Early Chemistry, 1924 (Box 51)
  - Storey, Thomas Andrew, William Henry Geer: Memoir of His Life and His Service to Physical Education, 1928 (Box 51)
  - Storey, Thomas Andrew, Papers 1902-1909 (Box 51)
  - Storey, Thomas Andrew, General Hygiene; Book 1: Constructive Hygiene, 1926 (Box 52)
  - Storey, Thomas Andrew, General Hygiene; Book 2: The Agents That Injure Health and the Carriers of Pathogens, 1926 (Box 52)
  - Strong, Edward K. Jr., Introductory Psychology for Teachers, 1920 (Box 52)
  - Strong, Edward K. Jr., Psychological Aspects of Business, 1938 (Box 52)
  - Strong, Edward K. Jr., The Psychology of Selling Life Insurance, 1922 (Box 52)
  - Stuart, Graham H., American Diplomatic and Consular Practice, 1936 (Box 52)
  - Stuart, Graham H., The Tacna-Arica Dispute, 1927 (Box 52)
  - Stuart, Graham H., Latin America and the United States, 1922 (Box 52)
  - Stuart, Graham H., Le Droit et la Practique Diplomatiques et Consulaires, 1935 (Box 52)
  - Stuart, Graham H., The Governmental System of Peru, 1925 (Box 52)
  - Suzzallo, Henry, Columbia University Teachers College Contributions to Education; No. 3: The Rise in the Local School Supervision in Massachusetts, 1906 (Box 53)
  - Tarshis, Lorie, Elementos de Economia Politica, 1950 (Box 53)
  - Taylor, Alonzo Englebert, University of California Publications, Pathology: On Fermentation, 1907 (Box 53)
  - Terman, Lewis M., The Measurement of Intelligence, 1916 (Box 53)
  - Thoburn, Wilbur W., In Terms of Life, 1899 (Box 53)
  - Timoshenko, Stephen P., As I Remember: The Autobiography of Stephen P. Timoshenko; translated by Robert Addis, 1968 (Box 54)
  - Tolman, C. F., Ground Water, 1937 (Box 54)
  - Townley, Sidney D. and Maxwell Allen, Descriptive Catalog of Earthquakes of the Pacific Coast of the United States, 1769-1928, 1939 (Box 53)
  - Treat, Payson Jackson, Japan and the United States, 1853-1921 (Box 53)
  - Treat, Payson Jackson, The National Land System, 1785-1820, 1910 (Box 53)
  - Tuttle, D. F., Redes Electricas, 1964 (Box 54)
  - US Government Report, Report of the Commission Appointed to Study the System of Education in the Public Schools of Baltimore, 1911 (Box 15)
  - US Government Report, Report of a Survey of the School System of Butte, Montana, 1914 (Box 15)
  - Van Patten, Nathan, Collected Papers; Vol. 1: 1921-1931 (Box 54)
  - Van Patten, Nathan, Collected Papers; Vol. 2: 1936-1939 (Box 54)
  - Van Patten, Nathan, Concerning "Condensed Novels;" written by Bret Harte, 1929 (Box 54)
  - Van Rysselberghe, Pierre and Th. De Donder, Thermodynamic Theory of Affinity: A Book of Principles, 1936 (Box 54)
  - Van Rysselberghe, Pierre and Th. De Donder, Thermodynamic Theory of Affinity: A Book of Principles; translated to French, 1936 (Box 54)
  - Veblen, Thorstein, Papers 1906-1909 (Box 54)
  - Walker, Robert A. and Floyd Cave, How California is Governed, 1953 (Box 54)
  - Ware, Sedley Lynch, The Elizabethan Parish in its Ecclesiastical and Financial Aspects, 1908 (Box 54)
  - Warner, Amos G., Some Experiments on Behalf of the Unemployed (Box 55)
  - Warner, Amos G., American Charities, 1908 (Box 55)
  - Warner, Glenn Scobey, Football for Coaches and Players, 1927 (Box 55)
  - Watt, Ian, Jane Austen: A Colledction of Critical Essays, 1963 (Box 55)
  - Watt, Ian, The Rise of the Novel, 1963 (Box 55)
  - Webster, David Locke et. al., General Physics for Colleges, 1923 (Box 56)
  - Webster, Hutton, Historical Selections, 1929 (Box 55)
  - Webster, Hutton, History of Civilization, 1940 (Box 55)
  - Webster, Hutton, History of Latin America, 1924 (Box 55)
  - Webster, Hutton, In Varying Moods: Epigrams and Other Verses (Box 56)
  - Webster, Hutton, Rest Days: A Study in Early Law and Morality, 1916 (Box 56)
  - Webster, Winifred Fry, Morals for Morons and Other Nonsense Verses, 1954 (Box 56)
  - Wentworth, Gerald O. et. al., The Accounting Process: A Program for Self-Instruction, 1963 (Box 56)
  - Whitaker, Albert C., Foreign Exchange, 1924 (Box 56)
  - Whitaker, Virgil K. and E. Bagby Atwood, Excidium Troiae, 1944 (Box 56)
  - Wilbur, Ray Lyman, Civilization; written by James Harvey Robinson, 1929 (Box 56)
  - Wilbur, Ray Lyman, National Advisory Committee on Education, Report October 1931: Federal Relations to Education (Box 57)
  - Wilbur, Ray Lyman, The Memoirs of Ray Lyman Wilbur, 1875-1949, 1960 (Box 58)
  - Wilbur, Ray Lyman adn Arthur Hyde, The Hoover Policies, 1937 (Box 58)
  - Wilbur, Ray Lyman and Elwood Mead, The Construction of Hoover Dam: Preliminary Investigations, Design of Dam, and Progress of Construction, 1933 (Box 57)
  - Wilbur, Ray Lyman and Northcutt Ely, The Hoover Dam Power and Water Contracts and Related Data, 1933 (Box 57)
  - Wilbur, Ray Lyman and William Du Puy, Conservation in the Department of the Interior, 1931 (Box 57)
  - Wilbur, Ray Lyman et. al., Social Education, Stanford Education Conference: Extent and Use of Natural Resources, 1939 (Box 56)
  - Wilbur, Ray Lyman et. al., Annual Reports of the Secretary of the Interior, 1929-1932 (Box 57)
  - Wilbur, Ray Lyman et. al., Annual Reports of the Secretary of the Interior, Fiscal Year Ending June 30, 1929 (Box 57)
  - Wilbur, Ray Lyman et. al., Annual Reports of the Secretary of the Interior, Fiscal Year Ending June 30, 1930 (Box 57)
  - Wilbur, Ray Lyman et. al., Annual Reports of the Secretary of the Interior, Fiscal Year Ending June 30, 1931 (Box 57)
  - Wilbur, Ray Lyman et. al., Annual Reports of the Secretary of the Interior, Fiscal Year Ending June 30, 1932 (Box 57)
  - Wildman, Murray Shipley, Money Inflation in the United States: A Study in Social Pathology, 1905 (Box 58)
  - Willis, Bailey, Historia de la Comision, 1943 (Box 58)
  - Willis, Bailey and Robin Willis, Geological Structures, 1934 (Box 58)
  - Winters, Yvor, The Anatomy of Nonsense, 1943
  - Woodward, Frederic Cambell, The Law of Quasi Contracts, 1913
  - Yotopoulos, Pan A., Allocative Efficiency in Economic Development: A Cross Section Analysis of Epirus Farming, 1967
- Pamphlets and Reprints, Series 2
  - Abbott, Nathan (Box 10)
  - Abott, Donald P. (Box 10)
  - Abramovitz, M. (Box 10)
  - Abrams, Alan M. (Box 10)
  - Abrams, Herbert L. (Box 10)
  - Abrams, Irving (Box 10)
  - Abrams, Leroy (Box 10)
  - Acrivos, Andreas (Box 10)
  - Addis, T. (Box 10)
  - Alden, Raymond MacDonald (Box 10)
  - Alderson, Harry E. (Box 10)
  - Aldrich, Putnam (Box 10)
  - Allan, Evelyn Wight (Box 10)
  - Allardice, R. E. (Box 10)
  - Allen, Clifford Gilmore (Box 10)